what are your thoughts on the JF
Revelation I think what they're going to
focus on is Cia surveillance activities
in Mexico City in October and November
of 1963 but don't forget that when
Richard Helms was the director of the
CIA he ordered most of those documents
to be destroyed illegally so if there
happened to be any Smoking Gun I think
it was chewed up in an industrial
grinder a lot of years ago they have a
giant furnace that powers CIA
headquarters so it's not part of the
local grid they just burn it we might
see some Revelations about RFK you know
Bobby Kennedy tells an interesting story
I told him you need to write this down
because this is historic he said that on
the day that his uncle was killed uh his
mom went to school to pick him up early
when they pulled into the driveway his
dad was standing in the driveway talking
to John mccon who was the CIA director
the kennedies and the mccon were very
very close so Bobby said when he got out
of the car he heard his dad say tell me
your people didn't do this